<Element name="WebProject" lowerName="web project"
		pluralLowerName="">
		<Description>
			A Web Project maintains the model information of your Web Application. 
			The project includes information about
			Domain Model and Web Model elements.
		</Description>
		<ActionRef label="Add Site View" />
		<ActionRef label="Add Service View" />
		<ActionRef label="Add Module Definitions" />
		<ActionRef label="Add Context Parameter" />
		<ActionRef label="Add Activation Expression"/>
		<ActionRef label="Add Property"/>
		<ActionRef label="Localize"/>
		<ActionRef label="Generate Layout Pages Only"/>
		<ActionRef label="Generate Logic Descriptors Only"/>
		<ActionRef label="Generate Selection"/>
		<ActionRef label="Generate and Run"/>
		<ActionRef label="Find Model Problems"/>
		<ActionRef label="Help"/>
		<PropertyCategory name="General">
			<Property label="Current Deploy Configuration">
It defines one of the local deploy configurations to be used to generate the project. 
When selected all the properties are automatically inherited from the configuration and rendered as read-only in the project.
&lt;p&gt; The Browse button <Button name="Browse"/> opens the Select Local Deploy Configuration dialog to choose or create a new configuration.&lt;/p&gt;
The Edit button permits to see and to edit the selected deploy configuration.
<Button name="Clear"/>
			</Property>
			<PropertyRef label="Output Path"/>
			<PropertyRef label="HTTP Port"/>
			<PropertyRef label="HTTPS Port"/>
			<PropertyRef label="HTTP Request Helper"/>
			<PropertyRef label="Default Application Encoding"/>
			<Property label="Default Server Encoding">
				Character encoding that the target application server uses for reading parts of
				incoming requests that do not specify an encoding.&lt;br/&gt;
				If 'Use Default URL Encoding' is checked, this is also the encoding used for
				&lt;i&gt;writing&lt;/i&gt; URLs.&lt;br/&gt;
				Default value: ISO-8859-1
				
				&lt;p&gt;For correct operation it is very important that this property value matches
				the configuration of the target application server.&lt;/p&gt;
				
				&lt;p&gt;Since request headers declare their own encoding inline and the body is
				read using the 'Default Application Encoding', the request URL is the only part
				of the request not specifying an encoding.&lt;/p&gt;
				
				&lt;p&gt;Therefore, the server encoding is used in practice just for
				&lt;i&gt;reading&lt;/i&gt; incoming request URLs. On the other hand, the encoding used
				for &lt;i&gt;writing&lt;/i&gt; URLs is ultimately controlled by the
				'Use Default URL Encoding' property.&lt;/p&gt;
				
				&lt;p&gt;If the two encodings do not match, it is possible for URLs to get corrupted,
				most notably affecting query string parameters. With 'Protect URL' checked, the server
				may even mistake a corrupted character for a security issue.&lt;/p&gt;
			</Property>
			<PropertyRef label="Server Name"/>
			<PropertyRef label="Use Default URL Encoding"/>
			<PropertyRef label="Max Upload File Size"/>
			<PropertyRef label="Resource Servlet Path"/>
			<Property label="Default WebModel Project">
			    The default web model project where the user is redirected accessing the enterprise application. 
			</Property>
			<PropertyRef label="Session Timeout"/>
			<Property label="Default Cookie Timeout">
			    The default cookie timeout in minutes.
			    A negative value (-1) means that the cookie is not stored persistently and will be deleted when the Web browser exits. 
			</Property>
		    <Property label="Current Running Profiles">
		    	The Running Profile(s) set on the Web Project and used during the editing and generation process. 
				If empty, the whole web project is considered.
		    </Property>
			<Property label="Database">
			    The source database.
			</Property>
			<Property label="Schema">
			    The source database schema.
			</Property>
			<Property label="Table Prefix">
			    If set, all the names of tables are prefixed with the specified value.
			</Property>
			<Property label="Job Thread Pool Size">
			    The number of threads that are available for concurrent execution of jobs.
			</Property>
			<Property label="Mail Provider">
			    The default SMTP Server used to deliver mail notifications.
			</Property>
			<Property label="Orientation">
			    Defines the locked screen orientation for the Mobile Application when running on the mobile device. 
				The default value is the device default orientation.
			</Property>
			<Property label="Full Screen">
			    If checked, the Mobile Application will be displayed in full screen mode when running on the mobile device.
			</Property>


			<Property label="Platform">
			    The device platform which the Notification Provider is configured for.
			</Property>
			<Property label="API Key">
			    The public API key generated on the Google Cloud Messaging website. This API key enables push notification for Android devices.
			</Property>
			<Property label="APNS Certificate">
			    The Certificate file generated on the Apple Developer Portal. This certificate enables push notifications for iOS devices.
                If unspecified it will be possible to send notifications only to the WebRatio Developer App.
			</Property>
			<Property label="APNS Certificate Passphrase">
			    The password required to use the APNS Certificate.
			</Property>
			<Property label="Sandbox">
			    If checked, the provider will use the APNS sandbox environment to dispatch messages.
			</Property>




			<Property label="Output Path" onlyForNatureId="com.webratio.ide.WebNature">
				The directory in which the Web Application is generated.
				The Browse button <Button name="Browse"/>opens the &lt;a href="/Reference/WizardsAndDialogs/OutputPathSelectionDialog"/&gt; that allows to select a valid directory.
				<Button name="Clear"/>
			</Property>
			<Property label="Login Definition" onlyForNatureId="com.webratio.ide.WebNature">
				The Action Definition set as the Login of the Web Application.
			</Property>
			<Property label="Back-end Base URL" onlyForNatureId="com.webratio.ide.WebNature">
				The endpoint URL of the back-end to be used for data synchronization. 
			</Property>
			<Property label="App Name" onlyForNatureId="com.webratio.ide.WebNature">
				The user-defined name for the Web Application.
			</Property>






		</PropertyCategory>
		<PropertyCategory name="Layout">
			<PropertyRef label="Style" />
			<PropertyRef label="Page Layout" />
			<PropertyRef label="Layout Manager" />
			<PropertyRef label="Grid Layout"/>
			<PropertyRef label="Frame Layout"/>
			<PropertyRef label="Cell Layout"/>
			<PropertyRef label="Attribute Layout"/>
			<PropertyRef label="Field Layout"/>
			<PropertyRef label="Event Layout"/>
			<PropertyRef label="Error Style Page"/>
			<PropertyRef label="Expire Style Page"/>
			<PropertyRef label="Login Style Page"/>
			<PropertyRef label="Component Configuration"/>
			<PropertyRef label="Old Resources"/>
			<PropertyRef label="Inherit Parameters"/>
		</PropertyCategory>
		<PropertyCategory name="Condition">
			<PropertyRef name="Visibility Condition" label="Grid Visibility Cond." />
			<PropertyRef name="Visibility Condition" label="Cell Visibility Cond."/>
			<PropertyRef name="Visibility Condition" label="Attribute Visibility Cond."/>
			<PropertyRef name="Visibility Condition" label="Field Visibility Cond."/>
			<PropertyRef name="Visibility Condition" label="Field Disable Cond."/>
			<PropertyRef name="Visibility Condition" label="Event Visibility Cond."/>
			<PropertyRef name="Visibility Condition" label="Event Disable Cond."/>
		</PropertyCategory>
		<PropertyCategory name="Security">
			<PropertyRef label="Protect URL"/>
			<PropertyRef label="Protect BLOB"/>
			<PropertyRef label="Digest Id"/>
			<PropertyRef label="Digest with Session Id"/>
			<PropertyRef label="Digest Type"/>
			<PropertyRef label="Digest Provider"/>
			<PropertyRef label="Digest Algorithm"/>
			<Property label="Module Domain Name">
				The domain name used to group the protected modules belonging to a specific web application.
		    </Property>
		    <Property label="Strict Module Access">
				If checked, the user has access only to modules associated with the current group.
		    </Property>
			<PropertyRef label="Enable Admin Area"/>
			<PropertyRef label="Admin Path"/>
			<PropertyRef label="Admin Username"/>
			<PropertyRef label="Admin Password"/>
		    <Property label="Model Element Domain Name">
		    	TODO missing description ... tbd
		    </Property>
		</PropertyCategory>
		<PropertyCategory name="Services/Jobs">
		    <Property label="Target Namespace URI">
			    The WSDL target namespace URI (default http://www.webml.org/webservices/wsdl).
			</Property>
            <Property label="SOAP Version">
                The SOAP protocol version used used by SOAP services (default 1.1).
            </Property>
            <Property label="SOAP Binding Style">
                The binding style used by SOAP services. 
                The possible values are: RPC Literal (default) or Document Literal. 
            </Property>
            <Property label="Enable REST Summary Page">
                If checked a summary page (RestSummary.do) describing REST web services is generated. 
            </Property>
			<Property label="Thread Pool Size">
			    The number of threads that are available for concurrent execution of jobs. If 
			    unspecified, a default value (5) is used.
			</Property>
			<Property label="Job Store Type">
			   It indicates where scheduling information (jobs and triggers) is stored.
			   The possible values are: 
			   &lt;ul&gt;
			      &lt;li&gt;Memory: scheduling information is stored within memory; this kind
of job store is fast and lightweight, but all scheduling information is lost when the process 
terminates.&lt;/li&gt;
			      &lt;li&gt;Database: scheduling information is stored within a relational database;&lt;/li&gt;
			   &lt;/ul&gt;
			</Property>
			<Property label="Job Database">
			    One of the databases defined in the project, where scheduling information is stored.
			</Property>
			<Property label="Job Schema">
				The database schema where the scheduling information is stored.
			</Property>
			<Property label="Job Table Prefix">
			    The prefix given to tables storing scheduling information; you can have multiple 
			    sets of scheduling tables within the same database if they use different table prefixes.
			</Property>
			<Property label="Clustered Job Store">
			    This property must be set to true if the Web application is deployed in
			    a clustered environment.
			</Property>
			<Property label="Job Group Name">
				The group name that jobs and triggers instances belong to. 
			</Property>
		</PropertyCategory>
		<PropertyCategory name="Localization">
			<PropertyRef label="Bundle Store Type"/>
			<PropertyRef label="Bundle Refresh Timeout"/>
		</PropertyCategory>
</Element>
		