<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<Component  type="operation" formBased="false" idPrefix="cnu" namePrefix="Connect " label="Connect" dataFlowSource="true" navigationFlowSource="true" dataFlowTarget="true" navigationFlowTarget="true" errorFlowSource="true" errorFlowTarget="true" successFlowSource="true" successFlowTarget="true" defaultLabel="Connect {label(id(get-source-class-id(id(@associationRole))))} to {label(id(get-target-class-id(id(@associationRole))))}"> 
    <AssociationRoleProperty label="Association Role" attributeName="associationRole" includeDerived="false" figureDisplayOrder="1">
	<Description xml:space="preserve">The association role for which the class instances must be
connected.</Description>
  </AssociationRoleProperty> 
  <ConditionalExpression label="Source Conditional Expression" classIdExpr="get-source-class-id(id(../../@associationRole))" elementName="SourceConditionalExpression" defaultPolicy="true" figureDisplayOrder="2" automatic="true"> 
	<Description xml:space="preserve">The set of selection criteria for retrieving the source instances of the
association role to which the target instances must be connected.
		</Description>
  </ConditionalExpression>
  <ConditionalExpression label="Target Conditional Expression" classIdExpr="get-target-class-id(id(../../@associationRole))" elementName="TargetConditionalExpression" defaultPolicy="true" figureDisplayOrder="3" automatic="true"> 
    <Description xml:space="preserve">The set of selection criteria for retrieving the target instances of the
association that must be disconnected from the source instances.</Description>
  </ConditionalExpression>
  <Description xml:space="preserve">A connect component enables the association of two sets of class instances in a 
given association role.
The instances to connect are identified using two conditional expressions conditions, 
one for each of the class that participates to the association role.
A connect component specification consists of two parts:
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The specification of the association role to which the operation refers.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;One conditional expression for each of the two classes participating 
to the association role (called &lt;i&gt;source&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;target&lt;/i&gt; class). 
The conditional expression identifies the set of class instances to be connected. 
If both conditional expressions retrieve a set of objects, all the possible objects pair are 
connected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</Description>
  <InputDescription xml:space="preserve" name="Condition-Name">The parameter associated to one of the Conditional Expressions
defined on the source or target class of the operation.</InputDescription>  
  <OutputDescription xml:space="preserve" name="Source (set of) Class-Name">The key attributes values of the object(s) of the source class of the association 
role that have been connected; this can be a subset
of the input objects of the operation, in case of partial or
total failure.</OutputDescription>  
  <OutputDescription xml:space="preserve" name="Target (set of) Class-Name">The key attributes values of the object(s) of the target class of the association
role that have been connected; this can be a subset
of the input objects of the operation, in case of partial or
total failure.</OutputDescription>
</Component>
