<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<Component  type="operation" formBased="false" idPrefix="cru" namePrefix="Create " label="Create" dataFlowSource="true" navigationFlowSource="true" dataFlowTarget="true" navigationFlowTarget="true" errorFlowSource="true" errorFlowTarget="true" successFlowSource="true" successFlowTarget="true" defaultLabel="Create {label(id(@dataBinding))}"> 
    <DomainClassProperty attributeName="dataBinding" includeDerived="false" figureDisplayOrder="1">
		<Description xml:space="preserve">The class for which a new instance is created.</Description>
	</DomainClassProperty>
    <BooleanProperty attributeName="bulk" label="Bulk">
		<Description xml:space="preserve">If checked, the component is able to perform multiple object creations at once.</Description>
	</BooleanProperty>
	<Description xml:space="preserve">A create component enables the creation of a class instance.
A create component specification consists of two parts:
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The specification of the class for which the instance must be created.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The values to use for the attributes of the new class instance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</Description>
	<InputDescription xml:space="preserve" name="Attribute Name">The value(s) to use for filling an attribute of the new class instance. 
In case of bulk creation, the rules driving the creation of instances are the following: 
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;if all the attribute values are arrays of length L, the operation exactly creates L different instances.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;if arrays of length L are inter-mixed with either arrays of length one or plain values, again L
     different instances are created; single values are replicated all over the L instances.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;it is an error if arrays of different lengths (greater than one) feed the operation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</InputDescription>    <InputDescription xml:space="preserve" name="1:N Association Name">The value to use to perform also a connect operation in the
same instruction.</InputDescription>  
  <OutputDescription xml:space="preserve" name="New Object">The key attributes values of the newly create object. The parameter is valid
only if the operation succeeds; therefore it cannot be used
in Error Flows.</OutputDescription>
</Component>
