<Element name="NavigationFlow" lowerName="navigation flow" pluralLowerName="navigation flows">
	<Description>
		A Navigation Flow 
		abstracts and generalizes the fundamental notion of hypertexts: the concept of anchor.
	</Description>
	<ActionRef label="Add Property" />
	<ActionRef label="Localize" />
	<ActionRef label="Go to Source"/>
	<ActionRef label="Go to Target"/>
	<ActionRef label="Straighten Connections" />
	<ActionRef label="Separate Overlapping Connections" />
	<ActionRef label="Open Generated Code" />
	<ActionRef label="Generate Layout Pages Only"/>
	<ActionRef label="Generate Logic Descriptors Only"/>
	<ActionRef label="Generate Selection"/>
	<ActionRef label="Find Model Problems"/>
	<ActionRef label="Help"/>
	<PropertyCategory name="General">
		<PropertyRef label="Identifier" />
		<PropertyRef label="Name" />		
		<Property label="Source/Source Toolbar" onlyForNatureId="com.webratio.ide.MobileNature">
			The component or toolbar from which starts the <ElementRef />.
		</Property>		
		<Property label="Source/Source Page">
			The component or page from which starts the <ElementRef />.
		</Property>		
		<Property label="Target" onlyForNatureId="com.webratio.ide.MobileNature">
			The component or toolbar to which ends the <ElementRef />.
		</Property>	
		<Property label="Target/Target Page" name="Target Component">
			The component or page to which ends the <ElementRef />.
		</Property>	
		
		<Property label="Target Action" onlyForNatureId="com.webratio.ide.MobileNature">
			The Action to which ends the <ElementRef />.
		</Property>	
		<Property label="Target Action">
			The component or toolbar to which ends the <ElementRef />.
		</Property>		
		
		<Property label="Target Toolbar" name="Target Component">
			The toolbar to which ends the <ElementRef />.
		</Property>			

		
		<Property label="Type">
			If the value is &lt;b&gt;Normal Navigation Flow&lt;/b&gt;, the flow is rendered as a clickable 
			anchor; if the value is &lt;b&gt;Automatic Navigation Flow&lt;/b&gt;, the flow is rendered as a 
			clickable anchor and the default output of the source component 
			is automatically supplied to the destination component when the 
			page that contains the flow is accessed; if the value is &lt;b&gt;Data Flow&lt;/b&gt;, 
			the flow is not rendered, but serves the sole purpose of transporting 
			parameter values.
		</Property>
		<PropertyRef label="Port Code" />
		<PropertyRef label="Binding" />
		<Property label="New Window">
			If checked, the navigation of the (normal interaction) flow opens a new browser window.
		</Property>
		<PropertyRef label="Preserve Form"/>
		<PropertyRef label="Custom Descriptor"/>
	</PropertyCategory>
	<PropertyCategory name="AJAX">
		<Property label="Enable AJAX">
			If checked, the flow performs a selective refresh of the source page at the end of
			navigation, updating the user interface only for the sub-set of components that changed.&lt;br/&gt;
			If the navigation ends on a different page, this property has no effect.
		</Property>
		<PropertyRef label="Component Computations"/>
		<Property label="On Failure Callback">
			Name of a global JavaScript function to invoke for handling errors in a server
			request performed asynchronously. The specified function does not replace the normal
			error handling behavior.
			&lt;p&gt;The function receives no arguments.&lt;/p&gt;
		</Property>
		
		<Property label="Open Window">
			If checked, the target page is opened inside a user interface window behaving as a child
			of the source page.
		</Property>
		<Property label="Replace Existing Window">
			If checked, the user interface window containing the source page is closed before opening
			the new window. This effectively causes the new window to replace the previous one under
			the same parent page.
		</Property>
		<Property label="Use Title">
			If checked, the opened window is displayed with a title.&lt;br/&gt;
			The displayed title depends on the 'Window Title' property.
		</Property>
		<Property label="Window Title">
			Text used as title for the opened window.&lt;br/&gt;
			Has no effect if 'Use Title' is unchecked.
		</Property>
		<Property label="Window Width">
			Width of the opened window in pixels.&lt;br/&gt;
			Default value: 200
		</Property>
		<Property label="Window Height">
			Height of the opened window in pixels.&lt;br/&gt;
			Default value: 300
		</Property>
		<Property label="Resizable">
			If checked, the opened window can be resized by the user.
		</Property>
    	<Property label="Auto Resizing">
			If checked, the opened window automatically resizes itself according to the content.
    	</Property>
		<Property label="Closable">
			If checked, the opened window displays a button to close it on the client-side.&lt;br/&gt;
			Note that no model flow is navigated when windows are closed this way.
		</Property>
		<Property label="Maximizable">
			If checked, the opened window displays a button to maximize it.
		</Property>
		<Property label="Minimizable">
			If checked, the opened window displays a button to minimize it.
		</Property>
		<Property label="Draggable">
			If checked, the opened window can be moved by the user.
		</Property>
		<Property label="Modal">
			If checked, the opened window blocks interaction with all parent pages until it is closed.
		</Property>
		<Property label="Class">
			The CSS class to apply to the opened window.
		</Property>
		<Property label="Show Effect">
			Effect to use for showing the opened window.&lt;br/&gt;
			Possible values are:
			&lt;ul&gt;
				&lt;li&gt;None,&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;li&gt;Appear,&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;li&gt;BlindDown,&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;li&gt;SlideDown,&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;li&gt;Grow.&lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;/ul&gt;
		</Property>
		<Property label="Hide Effect">
			Effect to user for hiding the opened window.&lt;br/&gt;
			Possible values are:
			&lt;ul&gt;
				&lt;li&gt;None,&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;li&gt;Fade,&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;li&gt;BlindUp,&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;li&gt;SlideUp,&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;li&gt;Shrink.&lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;/ul&gt;
		</Property>
		
		<Property label="Open Waiting Dialog">
			If checked, this flow displays a waiting dialog with a custom message while
			the navigation is occurring, closing it at the end.
		</Property>
		<Property label="Dialog Message">
			Key of the message to show in the waiting dialog.&lt;br/&gt;
			Default value: ajax.computingRequest
		</Property>
		<Property label="Dialog Show Time">
			The minimum time in milliseconds for which to show the waiting dialog.&lt;br/&gt;
			Default value: 1000
		</Property>
		<Property label="Dialog Width">
			Width of the opened waiting dialog in pixels.&lt;br/&gt;
			Default value: 200
		</Property>
		<Property label="Dialog Height">
			Height of the opened waiting dialog in pixels.&lt;br/&gt;
			Default value: 100
		</Property>
		<Property label="Dialog Class Name">
			The CSS class to apply to the opened waiting dialog.
		</Property>
	</PropertyCategory>
</Element>