<Element name="Trigger" lowerName="trigger" pluralLowerName="triggers">
	<Description>
		A trigger can be added to  
		&lt;a href="/Reference/ElementsReference/WebModelElements/Job"&gt;jobs&lt;/a&gt; in
		order to define at model time a pre-programmed schedule on which to run the job.&lt;br /&gt;
		&lt;br /&gt;
	</Description>
	<ActionRef label="Add Property" />
	<ActionRef label="Generate Logic Descriptors Only"/>
	<ActionRef label="Generate Selection"/>
	<ActionRef label="Find Model Problems"/>
	<ActionRef label="Help"/>

	<PropertyCategory name="General">
		<PropertyRef label="Identifier" />
		<PropertyRef label="Name" />
		<Property label="Schedule Policy">
			Specifies the schedule policy to use. Common policies are further configurable
			through the other properties. The &lt;b&gt;Custom Cron Expression&lt;/b&gt; policy
			enables the use of a custom cron expression for maximum flexibility.
		</Property>
		<Property label="Synchronous Execution">
		    In case of session event triggering (&lt;b&gt;On Session Create&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;On User Login&lt;/b&gt;)
		    indicates whether the job must be executed in a synchronous or asynchronous way.
		</Property>
		<Property label="Hours">
			For schedule policies requiring an exact time, specifies the hours part of the time
			as a number in the range 0-23. For the &lt;b&gt;Every X Hours&lt;/b&gt; policy, specifies
			the number of hours	between executions of the job.
		</Property>
		<Property label="Minutes">
			For schedule policies requiring an exact time, specifies the minutes part of the time
			as a number in the range 0-59. For the &lt;b&gt;Every X Minutes&lt;/b&gt; policy, specifies
			the number of minutes between executions of the job.
		</Property>
		<Property label="Seconds">
			For schedule policies requiring an exact time, specifies the seconds part of the time
			as a number in the range 0-59. For the &lt;b&gt;Every X Seconds&lt;/b&gt; policy, specifies
			the number of seconds between executions of the job.
		</Property>
		<Property label="Day of Week">
			For the &lt;b&gt;Once a Week&lt;/b&gt; policy, specifies the day of the week on which
			to execute the job.
		</Property>
		<Property label="Day">
			For policies requiring it, specifies a day of the month as a number in the range 1-31.
		</Property>
		<Property label="Month">
			For policies requiring it, specifies a month.
		</Property>
		<Property label="Year">
			For policies requiring it, specifies a year as a positive number.
		</Property>
		<Property label="Cron Expression">
			When using a predefined schedule policy, this property shows the expression used to 
			configure the underlying Quartz job scheduler. The &lt;b&gt;Custom Cron Expression&lt;/b&gt;
			policy allows the user to manually enter &lt;a href=&quot;http://wiki.opensymphony.com/display/QRTZ1/CronTriggers+Tutorial#CronTriggersTutorial-Format&quot;&gt;custom cron expressions&lt;/a&gt;.
		</Property>
	</PropertyCategory>
</Element>